get your initials out so you can ride
risk-free and that's one of the best
ways you can support a coin or a
community that you're in you get risk
free so you're not stressing out in a
coin and and you know being all
emotional and and that way the more
people in a coin actually get their
initial money out and are writing
risk-free stressfree the more successful
that coin can often be because the
holders they're not too affected by the
outcome now because they've already
secured their initial investment so I
highly encourage people as you're up
multiple if you're up 2x whatever X get
your initial investment out and it'll
it'll make you feel so much better and
more confident and then you can legit
the way I think of it is you're owning
digital real estate on this chain in the
form of a meme coin